linkpopularity.com 2017-11-28

# LinkPopularity.com: The Free Link Popularity Service

**Privacy Statement**

This web site is maintained by The PC Edge, 626C Admiral Drive, Annapolis MD 21401. Your privacy is important to us and we are firmly committed to protecting it.

**What information do we collect?** Â 

We collect information from you when you utilize our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter / update service.Â 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?** Â 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:Â 

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To process transactions

> We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes without your consent.

; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

; To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?** Â 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.Â 

**Do we use cookies?** Â 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

Third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from your website and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?** Â 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links** Â 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Terms and Conditions** Â 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at[ http://www.linkpopularity.com/consulting/serviceagreement.htm](http://www.linkpopularity.com/consulting/serviceagreement.htm)

**Your Consent** Â 

By using our site, you consent to ourÂ [websites privacy policy](http://www.linkpopularity.com/privacy.htm).

**Remove Your Name**

You may remove your name from our database at any time by clicking [here](http://www.linkpopularity.com/update.htm).

**Questions or Concerns**

The information that you provide us will be used only for the purposes described here. If you have any questions regarding this Policy Statement or the practices of this web site, please do not hesitate to [contact us](mailto:webinfo@pcedge.com).

  _Copyright 2014, The PC Edge, Inc._
